workonlineacademy.com 2016-04-22

# Privacy Policy

### 

Priceless Possibilities Privacy Policy

**HOW DOES PRICELESS POSSIBILITIES COLLECT AND USE MY INFORMATION?**

Priceless Possibilities may collect and use your personal information to provide you with information about the products or services that may be of value to you. Certain personal information that Priceless Possibilities collects about you may be publicly available via government records, telephone books, and other widely available media (i.e. the Internet). However, Priceless Possibilities treats all information that you provide to us as non-public. 

  1. Information that you provide. 
    * Priceless Possibilities collects the personal information that you provide when you sign up at one of our affiliate websites. 
  2. Information provided by the affiliate who owns this website. 
    * We may receive information from the affiliate about you after the affiliate has contacted you. Any information that we receive from affiliates is covered by this privacy policy and is considered non-public information. 
  3. Technical Information. We use technology to: 
    * Gather technical information from your Web browser (IP address, Browser type, Operating system); 
    * Set persistent cookies on your computer; and 
    * Collect information about your navigation through our website. 

We use this information for routine website maintenance; to establish that you are a unique user; to provide a personalized website experience; and/or for the purposes of assessing the effectiveness of our website, products and services. 

If you choose to disable cookies, you will still be able to access most of the website. However, as a security precaution, you may not be able to access certain information that could be used for email harvesting purposes. 

Top

* * *

**DOES PRICELESS POSSIBILITIES SHARE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES?**

Priceless Possibilities may share your personal information: 

  * With the owner of the website that you sign up at. 
  * As required by law. 

**Examples:** We may need to share your information with law enforcement or government agencies in response to a subpoena, state/federal audit or other similar circumstances. Additionally, the law requires that all mortgages and deeds of trust be recorded with the local county recorder's office 

Top

* * *

**CAN I OPT-OUT OF COMMUNICATIONS FROM PRICELESS POSSIBILITIES?**

You can OPT-OUT of communications from Priceless Possibilities by using the unsubscribe link that is available at the bottom of every email that is sent out by us. You may also opt out by sending an email to techsupport@pricelesspossibilities.com requesting that you be removed from all future mailings. 

Top

* * *

**WILL THIS PRIVACY POLICY CHANGE?**

To accommodate changes on the website, changing technology, and legal developments, Priceless Possibilities may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. The Last Revision Date of the Privacy Policy will be posted here.

**Last revision date:** May 31, 2005 

Top
